https://pushpedalpull.com/policy/

Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
You have no items to compare.
Menu
Search:
Search
New Exercise Equipment UP TO 50% OFF Up To 50% OFF EllipticalsUp To 50% OFF TreadmillsUp To 50% OFF BikesUp To 50% OFFStrengthCardio TreadmillsEllipticalsAdaptive Motion [AMT]Rowing MachinesExercise Bikes Upright BikesRecumbent BikesIndoor CyclingElectric BikesSpecialty Cardio Outdoor EllipticalsSteppers / ClimbersStretchingStrength Home GymsPlates and DumbbellsRacks & BenchesVibration PlatesAccessoriesPre-Owned Cardio TreadmillsEllipticalsExercise Bikes Upright BikesRecumbent BikesIndoor CyclingVibration PlatesStrength Home GymsPlates and DumbbellsRacks and BenchesCommercial Functional TrainersSelectorizedBrands PrecorLife FitnessTrueInspire WaterrowerConcept II Spirit FitnessStairmasterPower Plate3G CardioPowerBlock EscapeElliptiGoLifeCORE SchwinnTKO NuStep Troy BarbellStar TracFreeMotion Expresso SPRI eMotionPower SystemsServiceSolutions Trade-insRoom Design & PlanningFinancingContact us
Home
Policy
Policy
Push Pedal Pull ("P3") respects your personal privacy and is committed to adhering to federal and state privacy laws and industry guidelines in order to protect you and your identity. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle the personal information that you provide to us on this web site. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Push Pedal Pull Web Site, not to any other third party sites that may be accessible from here.
After reading this Privacy Policy you will know:
1) what information P3 collects from you  2) how P3 uses your information  3) what choices you have about how P3 treats your information  4) how P3 protects your privacy  5) how you can contact P3
Please be sure to read this Privacy Policy before using this Web Site or submitting information to us. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and your continued use of this Web Site is acceptance of such changes, so please check this area periodically for updates to this Privacy Policy.
1. INFORMATION PUSH PEDAL PULL COLLECTS FROM YOU
Active Information Collection  Like many other web sites, we actively collect information from our visitors both by asking specific questions on this Web Site and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via email. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc.).
Passive Information Collection  As you navigate through a web site, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without you actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as navigational data collection. Like most web site operators, we track IP addresses, use both session and persistent cookies, and assign Internet tags. Our system also automatically gathers information about the areas you visit on this Web Site and collects operational information about the technology you use, such as your browser, type of computer, operating systems, and Internet service providers. We passively collect information to understand what areas of this Web Site are most popular, which areas may require improvement, and what technologies are being used by our visitors. This information helps us to update and improve this Web Site. We also use this information for security purposes, to detect and to block security breaches and to provide you with a safe online environment.
2. HOW PUSH PEDAL PULL USES YOUR INFORMATION  Push Pedal Pull uses your personal information to enhance the operation of this Web Site and allow you to use all of its features. Push Pedal Pull may contact you about new features or products in which it believes you may be interested. Push Pedal Pull may disclose your personal information to the reputable vendors that assist us in processing information or delivering the items that our customers order. These vendors are restricted from using the information for any purpose other than helping us to provide products and services. Push Pedal Pull may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, online traffic patterns and related information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. Push Pedal Pull also will disclose any information that it is required to disclose by law or by an appropriate government authority.
Although Push Pedal Pull does not currently rent, sell, or otherwise share your information with third parties for purposes unrelated to this Web Site, it may do so in the future. If you do not want your information to be shared, you should contact us at p3@pushpedalpull.com.
3. CHOICES YOU HAVE ABOUT HOW PUSH PEDAL PULL USES YOUR INFORMATION  We strive to provide you with as many choices and as much control as possible regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information. You may also opt out of receiving marketing messages from Push Pedal Pull by notifying us at p3@pushpedalpull.com.
If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of this Web Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
You should review this Privacy Policy carefully, because if you do not agree with our practices, your ultimate choice is not to use this Web Site. Remember, by using any part of this Web Site, you accept and agree to our privacy practices. If we update this Privacy Policy, your continued use of this Web Site (following the posting of the revised Privacy Policy) means that you accept and agree to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
4. HOW PUSH PEDAL PULL PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION  We work hard to protect your personal information. We use both technical and procedural methods to maintain the integrity and security of our databases by storing data received via the Web Site in an access-controlled database.
This Web Site contains links to other web sites operated by third parties that may be of interest to you. We cannot control these third party sites, which may collect personal information from you. When you follow a link and leave this Web Site, you do so at your own risk.
5. HOW YOU CAN CONTACT PUSH PEDAL PULL  If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Web Site, please contact us at p3@pushpedalpull.com. You may also write to Push Pedal Pull at the following address: Push Pedal Pull, 515 N. Garfield Circle, Sioux Falls, SD 57104
Since 1985, Push Pedal Pull has been your local exercise equipment expert. We are an industry pioneer and a recognized leader in the sales and service of premium fitness equipment for both residential and commercial settings.
Today, we are one of the largest fitness equipment dealers in the country, with our 30 years of growth and stability in the specialty fitness industry.
Based in Sioux Falls, South Dakota, we also have 16 retail showrooms, 15 commercial sales representatives, and over 120 hard-working employees that serve thousands of residential and commercial customers throughout Arkansas, Nebraska, Oklahoma, Iowa, North Dakota, South Dakota, Kansas, Minnesota, Missouri, Western Wisconsin, Tennessee, Colorado and Wyoming. Over the years, we’ve earned the right to exclusively represent most of the fitness industry’s leading equipment manufacturers.
Our goal is to be your one-stop source for premium exercise equipment, home fitness solutions, commercial fitness solutions, onsite service and repair, preventative maintenance plans, fitness equipment delivery, equipment moves, product installation and training.
JOIN THE INSIDERS CLUB
Join today for exclusive access to news, tips and special offers
© Copyright 2020 Push Pedal Pull | 2306 West 41st Street Sioux Falls,SD 57105 888.861.8978 | Terms and Conditions | Policies | Sitemap
live chat software
